Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.17 01:40:30
[Narrator] Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
你已经无法为她做任何事了
You can't help her now.
你并不关心私人问题
You don't ask a lot of personal questions.
而且你非常难相处
And you're very hard to get to know.
Yes.
是的
With your reputation, Seattle Grace will become
以你多年的经验，seattle grace将成为
曼哈顿西部的知名产科医院之一.
one of the foremost neonatal hospitals.
我们这里有一个三级烧伤患者.
Got a third trimester burn victim, Dr. Bailey. I need help.
Dr. Bailey,我需要帮忙
你在我的领域有不错的天赋
You show a real gift with my specialty.
我会在这里呆上一阵子的
I'll be staying in town for a while.
再见,derek.
Goodbye, Derek.
再见,meredith.
Bye, Meredith.
想请我喝杯东西吗?
Do you wanna buy me a drink?
[Giggling]
当你还是孩子的时候,
[Meredith] When you were a kid, it was Halloween candy.
你喜欢万圣节的糖果.
你从父母那里骗来，然后一直吃到恶心
You hid it from your parents and ate it until you got sick.
这里就是... 你住的地方?
[Cristina] So, this is where you live?
[Giggles]
而在大学的时候，变成了猛烈的混合物
In college, it was the heady combo of youth, tequila, and, well, you know.
年轻，酒，和那个...你知道.
作为一个医生，你需要
As a surgeon, you take as much of the good as you can get,
尽可能的做到尽善尽美...
因为改正错误的机会,并不是经常发生
because it doesn't come around nearly as often as it should.
因为好事永远不是表面看起来那样
Good things aren't always what they seem.
太棒了.
That was amazing.
是啊,爽
Yeah.
什么东西太多了的话..
Too much of anything, even love, is not always a good thing.
即使是爱情...
也不会永远那么美好了
Did you...
你有(高潮吗?)...
恩
Yeah. I did.
- [Meredith] There's a boy in my bed. - [Cristina] What's his name?
我床上有个男人
叫什么?
Um... Steve.
Um,steve.
- Where'd you find him? - joe's.
你哪里找到的?
Joe的酒吧.
猜猜我在哪里
- Guess where I am? - Where?
哪里?
Burke's apartment. He went to the hospital.
Burke的公寓
他去医院了
[Spits]
他把我自己留在这里了
He left me here alone.
你要对他的东西彻底检查,对吧?
You're going through his stuff, aren't you?
哦,根本没有什么值得我检查的.
There's no stuff to go through. It's a freak show.
他这是个怪地方
You can do surgery in here.
我是说,你都能在这里做手术了
Oh...
他按照杜威图书分类法给他的书籍归类
He arranged his books using the Dewey Decimal system.
Mer,我害怕
- Mer, I'm scared. - Get out. Get out of the house now.
离开那里,现在就离开那公寓
和谁说话呢?
Who you talking to?
我要挂了
Uh... I gotta go.
[Phone beeps]
Uh...
Uh... I have to go take a shower.
我要去洗个澡
And when I get back, you won't be here. So, um... goodbye, Steve.
当我回来的时候,希望你就不在这里了
那么,再见了,steve.
新"西雅图未眠夜"啊
Another sleepless night in Seattle.
是啊,这次又是谁?背上长毛的家伙?
Who was it this time? "Hairy Back Guy"?
知道我想谁吗?
You know who I miss? "Inappropriate Facial Hair Guy."
那个胡须不对称的家伙.
You know, he did his own dishes.
知道吗他洗了自己的盘子?
"Tattooed Ass Guy" made coffee.
屁股上有文身的家伙还煮过咖啡呢
是啊,他是个看门的
Yeah, he was a keeper.
怎么了?
What? What? Meredith?
Meredith?
- I am over her. - OK.
我早不迷恋她了
Okay.
- I am. - Yeah, I can see that.
我的确放弃了
是啊,我看出来了
But, is she trying to set some kind of record?
尽管如此,她是在试图创造什么记录吗?
至少她还有个目标
At least she has a goal.
Oh. Oh.
Oh.
哦,他是新的哦
- He's new. - And I shall name him: "Running Guy."
那我就叫他"逃跑小子"吧
知道昨晚我听到Alex和谁一起回家来了吗?
You know who I heard Alex come home with last night?
你
- You. - I don't want to talk about it.
我不想聊这个
- [Chuckles] - I really do want to talk about it.
事实上,我挺想聊聊这个的
He doesn't want to talk about it because there were technical difficulties.
但是他不想
因为那个...技术上的困难
什么?
- What? - You know, he didn't... He...
那个,他没有...他....
-不 -别说了
- No. - Stop it.
你不许乱说话
You can't say anything.
George,别笑了
- George, stop it. - I...
我...下次我见到他的时候
I'm gonna at least think about making fun of him when I see him.
至少我能想想如何取笑他
他说他以前从没做过
- He said it never happened before. - That's what we all say.
哦,这是大家都在说的
我认真的,所有人都是这么说的
And I mean, "they." That's what "they" all say.
我不知道
I don't know. Maybe this relationship just isn't meant to be.
也许这段感情根本就不到那个地步
I mean, I just need some sex, George, you know?
我是说,我只是...
只是需要做爱罢了 george
明白吗?我不过...
I need sex now! You know what I mean?
我现在就要做爱.明白我说什么吗?
无论你怎么求我...
No matter how hard you beg, I am not doing you.
我也不会做你的
欢迎你的加入
- Nice to have you on board. - Thank you, Patricia.
谢谢patricia.
你工作自由
Your own service, a state-of-the-art NICU,
艺术级的工作待遇
and a salary that makes you one of the highest-paid surgeons in the northwest.
以及一份高薪-
足以让你成为西北地区最高收入的医生
- You better be worth it. - Quintuplets, Richard.
你最好对得起这薪水
五胞胎产妇,richard.对吗?
- That's a go. - Mother-to-be checked in today.
今早这个即将临盆的孕妇送了进来
Nothing I like more than a high-profile case.
没什么比一个特殊病例更让我喜欢的了
别把结论下的太早
Don't go calling the press in yet. It's a high-risk pregnancy.
这是个极度高危险的怀孕
Three babies are surgical. I'll need people from all departments.
至少三个婴儿是可以手术治愈的
事实上,我需要从所有的科系调人手过来帮忙
You're my star. Whatever you need.
你说了算
无论你需要什么
这航班上有餐点供应吗?
Is there meal service on this flight?
Robert martin,45岁,昏倒的时候撞击了头部
Robert Martin, 45, hit his head, causing a small subdural hemorrhage.
导致小面积脑硬膜出血
Also, uncontrolled eye movement and delirium.
同时伴有眼睛失控,以及暂时性精神狂乱
酒精和毒性测试均为阴性
Alcohol and tox screens were negative, but sodium level is 112.
但是他体内的钠指数只有112.
- A little too low for my taste. - [Martin] Hey! Hey!
我觉得有点低
hey. Hey!
Mr. Martin,你那边还好吗?
Mr. Martin, how are you doing in there?
我还在等我要的喝的呢.你是空姐吗?
I'm still waiting on that drink. Are you the stewardess?
我们马上就去叫空姐
We're called flight attendants now.
Hey!
Hey! Oh,看这里.
There it is. On his pituitary, it's a Rathke's cleft cyst.
在他的垂体上方,一个小小的裂开的囊肿.
-那么他是hyponatremic了(钠指数低于135mmol/l) -没错
He's hyponatremic. Thirst is a side effect.
经常性的口渴就是一个普遍的副作用
- Water's screwing up his sodium levels. - Causing his delirium.
水能够提高他的钠指数
并且导致他的精神错乱
How do you treat hyponatremia?
那么你如何治疗hyponatremia?
3%高渗亚生理盐水静脉注射
Three percent hypertonic saline solution IV, 300 CCs over three hours.
3个钟头内要注射300 cc以上
Great. Call me when he stabilizes.
做的好,带他回病房吧
稳定下来后叫我,做的不错dr. Karev.
- Nicely done, Dr. Karev. - Hey! When does the movie start?
Hey!
电影什么时候开始?
Dorie, this is Dr. Stevens. She'll be working with us.
Dorie,这是 dr. Stevens.
她会帮我跟进你的病情的
- The more, the merrier. - How far along are you?
-人越多越热闹 -显然.你怀孕多久了?
32周.
- 32 weeks. - How long is a normal gestation period?
一般的怀孕周期是多久?
40 weeks, but with twins 36 weeks is considered full term,
40周,但是如果是双胞胎的话
36周就算是满周期了
so with quints 34 weeks is considered extremely successful.
而就五胞胎来说,34周就算非常成功了
给他们一些退烧药就好了
Mom, give him some acetaminophen. It's in the medicine cabinet.
在药柜里面呢
I plan on going 36 weeks. No one's leaving this uterus until I say so.
我是计划到36周再生
谁也不能离开这子宫,直到我同意为止
积极想法的力量,恩?
Power of positive thinking?
恩,卧床修养期
That, bed rest and all your medical care.
以及所有你给我的医疗关怀
We're with the doctors now. So, I'll talk to you later.
医生现在在做检查呢,过会我再打给你
Okay,bye.
OK, bye.
adam有点发烧
[Sighs]
Adam's got a fever, so soon they'll all have a fever.
那将意味着过不了多久他们都会染上的
Mom won't make it through lunch.
我想妈妈在午餐时间搞不定这个了
We have four-year-old boys. Adam, Oliver, and Graham.
我们家里有4岁的男孩...
-adam,oliver和graham. -三胞胎? 你... 你们已经有了个三胞胎了?
Triplets? You already have triplets?
我猜当你们在服用那些避孕药的时候
When you take fertility pills, you should read the fine print.
真应该好好读读上面的说明
- Dr. Stevens... - I'm sorry, I just... I meant...
Dr. Stevens.
对不起,我只是,我是说..
It's OK. I'm used to it. I just really wanted a girl.
没关系,我都习惯了,我只是很想要个女儿
是啊,我们只是没想到会同时来5个女儿
- We just didn't bank on five girls. - But think of all the clothes.
但是想想那些美丽的衣服和小可爱们吧
- And all that pink cuteness. - That's your happy place, remember?
亲爱的,那是你高兴的地方,记得吗?
Oh, yeah.
Oh,yeah.
试着别把所有闯进你大脑的东西都说出来
Try not to say everything that pops into your brain.
当我把他们踢出去的时候他们总是看起来挺难过
[Sighs] They always look so sad when I kick them out.
[Both chuckle]
认真的问,为什么
Seriously, why do guys not understand that when you pick them up in a bar
男人都不明白当你在酒吧里遇到他们
and take them home for sex, there are no picket fences or kids in your future?
然后带他们回家上床
根本不意味着你们会有一个大房子和一群孩子的未来?
Burke把钥匙给你了?
- Burke "keyed" you? - I got freaking "keyed" before coffee.
得到咖啡之前弄到了一把钥匙
那怎么了?
- What is wrong with them? - They're like these 1950s debutantes.
他们就像50年代的社交活动那样
One dance, and there's a shotgun to your head.
跳支舞,然后冲你的头开枪
Meredith.
-你在这里工作? -你在这里干吗steve?
- You work here? - What are you doing here, Steve?
我有一点小问题
- I'm having a little problem. - "Steve," Steve?
那个"steve"的steve?
Actually, I'm having a big problem.
事实上,我遇到麻烦了
什么?
- What? - Steve, hi. Cristina.
Steve,hi. Cristina.
自从我和你... 它就持续勃起.
Ever since you and I... It won't go away.
Cristina!
- Cristina! - What? It's right there, looking at me.
怎么了? 它就在那里看着我呢.
呵呵,此时此刻我有好多话想和你说
There are so many things I could say right now.
你真是冠军.
Champ.
[& Psapp: Cosy in the Rocket]
Grey's Anatomy 210 Much Too Much
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译/听译:Parry Wong 校对:Parry Wong
风软论坛 荣誉出品 www.1000fr.com
你们觉得这严重吗?
Do you think it's serious? It hurts like it is.
-我疼的厉害 -你意识到这个有多愚蠢了吗?
You realize this is insane.
听着,我们必须把他藏在哪里
We have to stash him somewhere until we figure this out.
直到我们找出到底什么原因为止
- I can't have people finding out. - I'm not going down for this.
-我不能让这个传遍整个医院 -我不会到处传这个的
你弄坏了这家伙的小弟弟不是我的错
- It's not my fault you broke his penis. - You broke his what?
弄坏他的什么?快点... hey,hey.
别让我到处追你们,我这里可养着个孩子呢
Don't make me chase you down. I'm growing a person here.
我要去看看检查结果了
I gotta check on some labs.
看起来如何?
How's it look?
不错
- Not bad. - Not bad?
不错?
"Not bad" is good when you have five babies in your uterus.
不错就是很好
当你有5个孩子在你子宫里的时候
Oh.
[Sighs]
这是kate.
It's Kate. She kicks me so hard it's like a belly burn every time.
她踢我还挺狠的
每次都像肚子要破了一样
你已经给他们起好名字了?
You've named them already?
我知道你觉得我很疯狂
I know you think I'm crazy, or maybe just a little bit stupid?
或者也许只是 一点点愚蠢?
Mrs. Russell,对不起
Mrs. Russell, I'm sorry if I've offended you...
如果我做了什么冒犯你的事情
The only thing that will offend me is if you pretend
只有一件事情会冒犯我
就是如果你假装你从来没有评价过我
you didn't judge me immediately.
自从我们相遇的那刻起
我们会在一起共渡一段时间的
We'll spend a lot of time together, so we may as well be honest.
所以诚实点对我们会好一些对吗?
如果你能减少婴儿即使只是两个
If you had reduced the fetuses even by two,
其他3个就会在你子宫里孕育久一些
the others could've been carried longer, been more developed and healthier.
吸收足够的营养,并且健康的生下来
你是第16个告诉我这些话的医生了
You're about the sixteenth doctor who's told me that.
这个在这上面...
This one up here, this is Charlotte.
这是charlotte.
She's the stubborn one.
她是最顽皮的那个
Lodged under my rib cage and won't budge.
留在我的胸腔里面,不肯移动
而这边...
Over here, Lucy.
lucy.
她是个坏孩子
She's a badass.
如果她被踢到,她一定会踢回去.
She gets kicked, she kicks back.
Emily.
Emily, she has the hiccups almost every day.
她几乎每天都打嗝
[Dorie laughs]
而这边是julie. 她是个成熟的孩子
And over here is Julie, she's pretty mellow.
每过一小会,她就要翻身调整姿势
Every once in a while she just turns over,
然后现在我们又回到了...
which brings us back to Kate.
kate.
那个让你肚子爆炸的孩子
- Who gives you belly burn. - Every time she kicks.
每次当她踢我的时候
我们只是把他带来这里
We were just bringing him up here because he's got this problem.
因为他只是有这个....问题,看到了?
他只是个朋友而已.
And he's a... a friend.
你朋友吃什么了?
What did your friend take?
-吃什么? -那些勃起功能障碍的药物?
- Take? - Which erectile dysfunction drug?
-你吃... -绝对没有,我发誓
- You took... - Absolutely not, I swear.
-我们之间完全是自然反映 -闭嘴
- It was all natural between us. - Shut up.
你这种情况叫做priapism(阴茎持续勃起症)
Your condition is called priapism,
一般是因为过度服用e.d.s(勃起功能障碍药物)
usually brought on by the overuse of EDs.
我什么都没吃
I didn't take anything.
我们只能相信你所说的
We'll have to take your word for it. There's no test to see if you're lying.
因为如果你一直撒谎的话,根本没任何测试可以看到
We'll have to look for other causes.
我们需要找出其他成因
很多检查需要做
There'll be lots of labs, lots of procedures.
还有很多...其他程序...
疼痛程序...
Painful procedures.
这测试会让你觉得,恨不得就没长过小弟弟
Procedures which might make you wish you never had a penis.
你确定你不想改变你的说法?
- Sure you won't change your story? - I swear I'm clean.
我发誓我是清白的
好吧Grey,去开始做他的测试吧
All right. Grey, start his workup.
做一些血测试,注射一些度冷丁来止痛
Get some blood. Get him some meperidine for his pain.
你的朋友现在已经肯定他的说法了
As of now, your friend is admitted.
Dorie russell...将要产下五胞胎
Dorie Russell, she's giving birth to quints.
恩richard说了我们要随时侯命
Richard said we were on standby.
这没什么,真的.因为这并不是
Which is no problem. It's not like I have a neurosurgery department to run.
好像我有个神经外科或者其他什么忙着要管理一样
是啊,很明显我们的科都在她的管理之下
Yes. Apparently our departments are at her disposal.
你们现在有时间和妈妈聊聊吗?
Do you have time to talk to the mom? I want her to meet all her surgeons.
-我想她见见其他手术组的成员 -好的,没问题
- Yes, no problem. - I'll come by after I finish in the OR.
我一从手术室出来就去
- Thank you, Dr. Burke. - Sure!
-谢谢dr. Burke -没问题
我没听到你今早离开酒店房间
I didn't hear you leave the hotel room this morning.
我在早饭的时候想你了
I had an early surgery.
我有一个很早的手术
你确定就因为这个?没其他了?
You're sure that's all? Nothing's wrong?
没有,就像我说的,我只是有个很早的手术而已
No, like I said, I had an early surgery.
Okay.
OK.
我觉得像一只搁浅的鲸鱼一样
[Sighs] I feel like a beached whale.
Dorie,这是dr. Shepherd. 他是我们的神经科主任
Dorie, this is Dr. Shepherd, he's our head of neurosurgery.
-Hi,dorie -Hi. 又一个dr. Shepherd.
- Another Dr. Shepherd? - He's my husband, actually.
-事实上他是我的老公 -真的吗?
Seriously? Wow, look at you two. Everybody must hate you.
哦,看看你们俩
大家肯定都嫉妒你俩
哦,你可不知道
[Both] You have no idea.
dorie,
Anyway, Dorie, Dr. Shepherd wants to talk to you about Baby "C."
dr. Shepherd想和你谈谈婴儿c.
-Lucy. -是的lucy有脑水肿
- Lucy. - Lucy has hydrocephalus.
这因为累积了过多的
It is a build-up of cerebrospinal fluid on the brain.
脑脊髓液而流到大脑形成的
OK, and that means...
好吧,那将意味着...
The fluid puts pressure on the baby's brain,
过多的液体积聚而成
然后压力推向婴儿的大脑
which could result in brain damage.
这个能导致脑损伤
好消息是,我们发现的早
Here's the good news.
We caught it early. We can take care of it quickly.
我们能很快的处理好这个
How?
如何处理?
I'll install a shunt to drain the fluid.
我将会做一个手术使液体排出
没有任何并发症
You're looking at a full recovery.
而且你会完全康复
- No brain damage? - No brain damage.
-没有脑损伤? -没有
好的,真的...
OK, really, couldn't you have led with that?
你就不能从好消息开始说吗?
说的好.
Good point.
这是什么?
What the hell is this?
钥匙
- It's a key. - Why?
-为什么 -为什么是钥匙?
Why is it a key? Are we feeling existential this morning?
我们今早讨论存在主义哲学了吗?
如果一把钥匙打开一把锁,而没人要这把钥匙
If a key turns in a lock, and no one asked for the key or even wanted it,
或者即使要这钥匙
does it make a sound?
不会发出声音吗?
Hey.
Hi.
我要把握这个机会
I'm going to take this opportunity to be someplace else.
离开你
-Steve的结果出来了,全部没问题 -如何?
- Steve's labs came back clean. - So?
那么某人需要做血管收缩
So, someone needs to induce vasoconstriction.
哦,真是有趣的词汇
Nice try with the fancy word. He needs an enema and the answer is "no."
他需要灌肠,答案是不
我不能做这个
I can't do it.
哦算了吧
You let a guy you picked up in a bar see you naked
你让一个从酒吧带回来的男子看你裸体
-但是你不能帮他灌肠? -完全两码事
- and you can't give him an enema? - Uncalled for.
我紧张而乖僻的.
- Well, I'm keyed up and cranky. - I'd do it for you.
我会帮你做这个的
Oh, really? You'd give Burke an enema?
是吗?你会帮burke灌肠?
-是的 -是吗?
- Yes. - Uh-huh.
-也许 -哦?
- Maybe. - Mm-hm.
不会做,但是这不是重点
No. But that's not the point.
Oh,yeah. Okay.不如这样
Oh, yeah. OK, here's how it goes.
我帮你这次
I do this for you and you do every enema I'm assigned to for a month.
-然后你帮我做这个月我所有分到的灌肠病人 -成交
Deal.
看来你是真不想做这个啊
You really don't wanna do this.
卖家中介那边有什么消息吗?
- Have we heard from the seller's agent? - I've been calling.
我整个早上都在联系
Mr. Martin, it's good to see you back on solid ground. I'm Dr. Shepherd.
Ah,mr. Rtin. 真高想看到你恢复正常
-我是dr. Shepherd. -我的助手doyle ss
My assistant, Doyle, says I passed out and hit my head.
我昏倒了而且撞了我的头
This guy says it's some kind of cyst.
这家伙说什么囊肿.
- I want you to say when I can leave. - A Rathke's cleft cyst.
-我想要你告诉我什么时候我可以出院 -早期裂口囊肿
管他呢
- Whatever. - A congenital tumor on your pituitary.
那是个先天瘤在你的垂体上
- Is it treatable? - You'll need surgery.
-是可治愈的对吗? -你需要做手术
我想要帮你做一个endonasal手术
- I'm gonna use an endonasal approach. - Endonasal?
Endonasal? Mm-hmm.
You're going to pull it out through my nose?
-你要把那东西从我鼻子排出来? -是的
查查他的声誉度
Look him up. Check his credentials.
这是很小的入侵式手术
It's minimally invasive so there won't be scarring.
-所以不会有任何疤痕留下 -很好,那么什么时候?
- Good. So, when? - When we stabilize your sodium levels.
一旦我们完全稳定住你的钠指数的时候
- That means no more water. - I'm thirsty.
-那意味着不能喝过多的水 -我渴
这是脑瘤的副作用
It's a side effect. We'll keep you hydrated intravenously.
我们会保持你的液体经脉注射
OK?
Right. Okay?
你tmd觉得自己在干吗?
What the hell are you doing?
我只是按照医生的嘱咐.
I'm just following the doctor's orders.
我无法相信这个要发生
- I cannot believe this is happening. - Try being me.
试着以我的角度想想
I mean, you meet someone in a bar, you have a few drinks, a few laughs,
我是说,你在酒吧遇到某人
你喝了一些酒,讲了一些笑话
在车里做爱
- you make out in the car... - Roll over to your side.
翻过去你那边,另外一边
Other side.
把你的膝盖抬到前胸上来
- Bring your knees up to your chest. - You have a good time.
你过了段快乐时光.
Spend the night, wake up the next morning and...
黑夜放纵,早上醒来
然后... okay!
- OK! - Mm-hm.
[Woman on PA]
你还不和我说话吗?
- Still not talking to me? - You gave me syphilis.
你把梅毒传给我
而且我在和你说话了
And I am talking to you. I just don't have anything to say.
我只是没话可说
george怎么样了?
- How's George? - O'Malley's a fetus.
O'malley是婴儿
He's all whiny and afraid of the light.
他总是嘀咕不停,而且害怕灯光
你没告诉他我和你上床了,这是个大事情
So you didn't tell him you were doing me. Big deal.
最小的暴露,这是我的政策
Minimal disclosure, that's my policy.
Hey. 我到处找你呢
Hey. I've been looking for you.
Hey.
我在跟着那五胞胎的病例
- I'm on the quints case. - Yeah, I heard.
我听说了
They'll need multiple surgeries.
是啊,他们需要
I put you on the pager list. So you're in too.
多重手术,一旦他们生下来
我把你的名字写在外援名单里了,那么你也会加入的
Yeah, I kind of got my own cases to worry about, so...
是啊,我还有我自己的病人
来担心照顾,所以...
okay,alex... 是我吗?
OK, Alex, was it me?
因为我们看起来应该有段正常的时光
Because we seemed to be actually having a normal time, a good time.
快乐的时光.
Yeah, we were having a good time.
是啊,我们的确过的很愉快
Well, then, was it me? Was it something I did?
那么是因为我吗?是因为我做了什么或者...
听着,不是因为你,好吗?
It wasn't you, OK? It was just...
是因为...
Look, I didn't feel like doing it. I was tired, you know.
我只是不想做那个而已
我很累,你知道?
那么你今晚想做吗?
Well, do you feel like doing it tonight?
恩...
[Short laugh]
我今晚值班,那么...
- I'm on call, so... - [short laugh]
好吧...
OK. Well, do you feel like doing it now?
你想现在做吗?
什么,现在?
Right now?
好多人都在这医院里做爱
People have sex in this hospital all the time.
听说那五胞胎了吗
- You hear about the quints? - Yeah, I heard.
恩,听说了
恩,我要参加那手术
I gotta get in on that.
是啊,那是addison的.
Yeah, well, that's Addison, so I'm guessing I don't stand a chance.
所以我猜我是不会被选中的.
你是如何弄坏那家伙的小弟弟的?
So how do you break a guy's penis?
你知道steve?
You know about Steve?
为什么我遇到的每个人
Why does every guy I meet
都有着与众不同的恶梦似的羞辱?
come with his own unique set of nightmarish humiliations?
也许是因为量?
- Maybe it's a matter of volume. - Volume? What's that supposed to mean?
量? 你什么意思?
I'm just... There's quality and then there's quantity.
只是,你知道,质量和数量
你的意思是我和太多的男人上床了?
So, you think I'm sleeping with too many guys? You think I'm some kind of slut?
你认为我是什么荡妇?
I think you are taking some risks.
我认为你在冒险.
I think you'll find yourself in some guy's basement
我认为你会在什么人的地下室的角落里找到你自己
正被安排着,在皮肤上涂满乳液
being ordered to do things or you'll get the hose again.
-或者你又穿上一双长筒袜 -别说了
- Come on. - I'm talking.
我认为...对不起我还没说完
So you're not over Derek. You want to be, but you're not.
所以你并没有忘记derek.你想忘记,但是你没有
你在试着找某些代替品
You're trying to find a replacement, a way to feel better.
某些暂时性的解决方法来让自己感觉好过些
But it's not going to work because a future of meaningless one-night stands
但是并没有成功,而且也不会成功
因为一场无意义的一夜情的未来
或者有问题的小弟弟,都不是你想要的东西
and problematic penises is not what you want.
你要的是更好的
You want better, and you deserve better.
而且你值得更好的
不是所有人都是个恶梦
And not every guy is a nightmare.
如果是我的原因,告诉我是因为我
- If it's me, just tell me it's me. - It's not you.
并不是你
Well, then is it a medical thing, or a problem?
那么是医学的问题了
或者.. 或者什么疾病?
Because guys have problems sometimes.
因为男人有时候有问题
我没病.
I don't have a problem.
回来
Get back down here. We're gonna do this until we do it.
我们继续做,直到做成了为止
好吧
OK.
[Giggles]
[Pager beeps]
Oh...9-1-1. 对不起
911. I'm sorry.
该死
Damn it.
你去哪里了?
- Where have you been? - I um... I... The nurse was here.
我...
护士在这里呢
I've loaded her up with magnesium. Start monitoring her for toxicity.
我放了一些镁在这里
然后开始监视她的毒性测试
It's too soon. They can't come yet.
哦,太快了,他们不能出来
妈妈说graham开始呕吐了
Mom says Graham started puking.
这是什么?怎么了?
What is it? What's going on?
Dorie开始宫缩,婴儿们的情况稳定
- She's having contractions. - Vital signs are stable.
但是你的胎盘下垂
Your placenta is laying low. We'll keep an eye on that.
我们会继续观察
We want them in there longer.
我们想要这些孩子尽可能久的留在子宫里
How, if she's already having contractions?
如果她开始宫缩的话如何留着他们?
没关系,亲爱的,他们可以做到
They can stop them. You're going to Trendelenburg me, right?
你要帮我做trendelenberg,对吗?
Yes, I am. You've done your reading, Dorie.
是的我会的,你读了好多相关材料,dorie.
他们对三胞胎也是这样做的
I did it with the triplets.
重力,记得吗,tom?
Gravity, remember, Tom?
那时候就做的很好,现在也会没事的
It worked fine then and it'll be fine now.
继续犹豫吧,tom.
Hang in there, Tom. No time for second thoughts now.
现在甚至没有一秒钟可让你思考
We didn't think that we'd survive a week with the boys, and we did.
我们第一周的时候都没想过可以和孩子们一起活下来
但是我们挺过来了,而现在我们会和女儿们再次活下来的
We'll be the same with the girls. We're ready.
准备好了
这就是我们现在所能做的
[Sighs]
That's all we can do for now. Dr. Stevens, are you on call tonight?
Dr. Stevens,你今晚值班吗?
不是
- No. - You are now.
你现在是了
灌肠不起作用.
- Enema didn't work. - Enema didn't work?
灌肠不起作用?灌肠不起作用
Enema didn't work.
那可是个非常棒的灌肠
Huh.
- It was an excellent enema. - So, what's the next step?
下一步该怎么办?
A needle aspiration.
扎针
扎针?
A needle? My penis?
我的小弟弟?
We have to drain the blood.
我们需要放血
不可以,绝对不行,算了吧
No way! No! Forget it!
那么你就会阳痿,
Then you're looking at impotence, penile infarction, or gangrene.
阴茎僵死或者腐败
- So if you want it to fall off... - No. No, I really don't want that.
如果你想它倒下来...
不,不,我真的不想要这个
那么让我们开始吧,什么让它起来,一定会有东西让它倒下的
Then let's get to it. What goes up must come down.
我感觉恶心
- I feel nauseous. - [Blows]
往后躺,闭上眼睛,试着放松自己
Just lie back, close your eyes, and try to relax.
如果我能放松的话,我就不会在这里了
If I could relax, I wouldn't be here!
[Woman] Doctor.
他怎么样了?
How is he?
手术排到明天了,所以..
- Surgery's scheduled for tomorrow. - Anything I can do?
还有什么需要我做的吗?
Don't let him drink any water. Even if he begs.
别让他喝水,即使他恳求
有什么家人需要我们联络的吗,朋友?  没有
Any family we should contact?
他不太擅长和其他人相处
- No. - Friends?
He doesn't get on with most people. Not big on social skills.
不太擅长社交   悲哀的家伙
- Sad guy. - Well, he has me.
他有我,3年的助手
Three years as his assistant. I guess I'm his friend.
我猜我是他的朋友
Doyle!
如果我把钥匙还给你会怎样?
What if I just give him back the key?
他会很难过   那如果我根本不用呢?
- He'll be hurt. - What if I don't use it?
这样说来,如果你没有想过要用它
If you had no intention of using it, you shouldn't have taken it.
你就跟本不该拿走它
Come on. Fishing a key out of a cup isn't like some binding legal contract.
算了你
从咖啡杯里钓上来一把钥匙
会不会像是什么法律约束的契约?
你男朋友把他家钥匙给你了?
Your boyfriend gave you a key to his place?
他为什么会说话?
Why's he talking?
我只是说说
The guy put himself out. He's taking the next step. You can't not use it.
一个男人都做了这些了,就是打算好下一步该怎么办了
你不能不用
Do you think you might not be in the best position right now
你有想过你此时此刻并不是什么好姿势
来建议我如何处理感情吗?
to be handing out relationship advice?
他把钥匙给你了,你带走了
Hey, he offered the key, you took the key.
只是因为我...
Just because I'm...
快看啊
Look at that!
恭喜
Congratulations. You're flaccid.
你软下来了
从没想过我是如此高兴听到这句话
Never thought I'd be so happy to hear that.
[Man on PA] Dr jones to Radiology. Dr jones to Radiology.
Dorie? Tom?
Hey,dorie,tom,
Hey, Dorie. Tom, this is Dr. Burke, he's the head of cardiothoracic surgery,
这是dr. Burke.
他是心胸外科主任
and Dr. O'Malley, who'll be assisting him.
以及帮助他的dr. O'malley
Dr. Burke想和你聊聊关于emily的心脏手术
Dr. Burke wanted to talk about Emily's heart surgery.
Emily需要心脏手术? 是的
- Heart surgery? - Yes.
你的女儿得了一种叫做
She has a condition called hypoplastic left heart syndrome.
左心室发育不全的综合症.这个手术就是要扩大它
The surgery will be extensive, and the odds are...
而成败几率是...
- We don't believe in odds. - Good. Neither do I.
我们不相信几率.   很好,我也不信
但是重要的是你们都明白
But it's important that you understand medically what's going on.
在你们女儿身上发生的医学转变
After she's born, there won't be much time to ask questions.
她出生之后,就没有时间再问问题了,所以...
okay.
OK.
我们在听.
- We're listening. - What's wrong with Emily's heart?
emily的心脏怎么了?
The left-side chambers are underdeveloped.
左侧的心室是发育不完全的
而且,用来连接两个心室的
And the mitral valve, which connects these chambers, is abnormally narrow.
二尖瓣
非正常的狭窄
[Chimes]
[Burke coughs]
钥匙
It's a key.
只是钥匙?
- Just a key? - Just a key.
只是钥匙
Good. Good. Good.
那好
很好
或者...
Or you could start thinking about moving in with me.
你可以开始想想搬来和我一起住
[Elevator chimes]
Sorry.
[Phone rings]
别怪我.
Don't mind me.
doyle怎么了?
- What's up with Doyle? - [Sighs] I had to fire him.
我必须炒了他
给我些水,我要脱水了
Get me some water. I'm drying up.
是啊,这是那瘤在说话
Yeah, well, that's the tumor talking. The IV is keeping you hydrated.
给你的静脉注射会保持你体内的水量
你要开除doyle? 他看起来是个不错的人
So why'd you fire Doyle? He seemed like a good guy.
我从他的眼睛中看到他再也不尊重我了
I could see it in his eyes. He didn't respect me anymore.
他认为他是你的朋友
He thought he was your friend.
朋友? Doyle?
- Friend? Doyle? - Right. You don't have any friends.
哦,对啊,你没有任何朋友
If I did, I wouldn't let them see me like this.
如果我有,我不会让他们看到我这样的
疾病是虚弱的象征
Illness is a sign of weakness.
一旦他们看到了,他们再也不会像从前那样对待你了
Once they see it, they look at you differently. You're a hotshot doctor.
我是说,你是个急功近利医生.
我肯定你不愿意让其他在这里的急功近利的医生
I'm sure you don't let the other hotshot doctors
知道任何你的问题
- know about your problems. - I'm a hotshot doctor.
不,我是个急功近利的医生,但是我没有任何问题
I don't have any problems.
你可能也没什么朋友
Probably don't have any friends either.
哦我的上帝
Oh, my Lord.
Oh, child.
别告诉我
- Don't tell me. - The flag is flying once again.
旗帜又迎风飘扬起来咯.
Hey, nothing I did.
嗨,我什么都没做
We've tried everything. It must be neural.
我们已经试过所有办法了,所有那肯定是神经性的了
神经性?
- Neural? - She already called for a consult.
她已经叫人来会诊了
会诊?你找人来为这神经性会诊?
A consult? You called Neuro for a consult?
嗨,不是我的错,是你弄坏了这小子的小弟弟
It's not my fault you broke the boy's penis.
大家好
Hello, everybody, what's up?
怎么了?
这..问题什么时候开始的?
Hm. So when did this problem begin?
我昨晚勃起了
Well, I had an erection last night and woke up with one this morning.
然后今早起床的时候又一次
Dr. Shepherd, if you don't need me,
dr. Shepherd,如果你不需要我的话
另外一个dr. Shepherd需要我过去为五胞胎会诊
the other Dr. Shepherd needs a consult on one of the quints.
不用了,我们很好
Yeah, no, we're fine. So when did you last ejaculate?
你昨晚是如何射精的?
我不太确定 Meredith?
I'm not sure. Meredith?
恩,我要过去帮 dr. Bailey.
Oh, I'm... I'm going to go with Dr. Bailey.
Meredith,我们是几点....
Meredith, what time did we, uh... you know...
你知道
是的,meredith,你们俩什么时候...
Yes, Meredith, what time did you two...
[amplified heartbeats]
[Printer whirs]
在这里,脐突出
Here it is. Right there, the omphalocele.
是啊,看看这个
- Look at that. - That's the scariest word yet.
那可是个让人惊慌的词哦
All it means is some of the baby's organs are in a sac outside its body.
那个意思是,一些婴儿的内脏
在它体外的一个囊内成长. Cristina!
"那个意思"?
- Cristina! - "All it means"?
她的内脏在她的体外.
Her organs are growing outside of her body? That's "all it means"?
那就是所有的意思?
- It's going to be OK. - I'll remove the sac membrane
会没事的
我会移除包括内脏在内的囊隔膜
containing the organs, make a small incision in the baby's abdomen
在婴儿的腹部切开一个小的切口
然后再放内脏进去
and put them back inside.
Oh,julie.
[Sighs]
她是最安静的孩子了.
Julie.
She's the quiet one.
什么让你认为...
What makes you think... What makes you think we can live together?
什么让你认为我们可以在一起生活?
你根本不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我了解你喜欢11层刀刃为你的i和d
I know that you prefer an eleven blade for your I and Ds.
我了解你喜欢说"pick ups"来代替 "forceps."
I know you prefer to say "pick-ups" instead of "forceps."
我了解你喜欢你的咖啡
I know you like your coffee from the cart by the front entrance
从门口前面那推车上买来的
better than the coffee in the cafeteria. I know you.
比自助餐厅的好,我了解你.
这些都是小事情....不过是细节
Those are little things. Just details.
我了解
I know you.
你不想搬来.
You don't want to move.
但是我不能一直做那个主动的人
But I can't always be the one that takes the step.
再多 一步的话,我就放弃了
Any more steps, and I'm walking away.
Mr. Martin!
Mr. Martin! Mr. Martin, please!
Mr. Martin,请回答!
Mr. Martin,你听到医生说的了,拜托!
Mr. Martin, please, you heard what the doctors said.
我不需要医生,不需要!
- [Mr. Martin] I don't need any doctors. - Open the door, Martin.
开门,martin.
I'm an island. A beautiful island surrounded by water.
我是一座岛屿
一座美丽的被水环绕的岛
你想怎么做?shepherd只给了我一个任务...
- What do you want to do? - Shepherd gave me one job to do.
就是别让这家伙喝水   需要我呼他吗?
Keep this dude from drinking water.
不用,我能处理,去拿些镇静剂来
- Do you want me to page him? - No.
把这层的水都停了
Get some restraints and turn the water off to the floor.
Martin,开门!
Open the door!
你的ct结果显示你有个瘤在脊椎底部
Your CT shows a tumor on your lower spine,
并且正压迫着你的神经.
which is pressing against your cavernous nerve, which is causing the erection.
导致你的勃起
瘤?   是的
[Steve] A tumor? Right.
瘤...那么...
A tumor? So, I should be scared, right?
我应该害怕,对吗?
这是...这是应该害怕的时候
This is the time for "scared."
会没事的.
Um... It's going to be fine.
dr. Shepherd会给你做个手术.
Um, Dr. Shepherd is gonna schedule surgery.
是的,我会取出那个瘤
I'll remove the tumor and everything should return to normal.
然后所有都会恢复到正常.     "正常"的正常?
我已经叫了一位秘尿科医生过来和你谈谈,但是是的...
"Normal" normal?
I have a urologist on his way up to talk to you, but yes, "normal" normal.
"正常"的正常
你能给我妈妈打电话吗?
Can you call my mom?
她的号码在我钱包里
Her number is in my wallet.
让她来,但是别告诉她那瘤
Don't tell her about the tumor. I don't want to scare her. She'll be flying.
我不想在她上飞机前吓坏她
Sure. OK.
好的
你们约会多久了?         我们没约会
- When did you start seeing each other? - We're not... seeing each other.
昨晚在joe的酒吧认识的.
We met last night at Joe's.
joe的酒吧?
Joe's Bar?
有一次我遇到一个女孩在那里
Mm-hm.
I met a girl there once myself.
很久以前
A very long time ago.
水停了!
The water's off. We'll just have to wait until he sobers up.
我们只能等到他清醒过来.
His sodium levels will drop too low.
不,他的钠指数会降的很低
[Gulping]
[Gobbles]
不,别管我!
No! No!
Leave me alone!
让我回去!
Let me go back. I need the water. I need it!
我要喝水,我要水!
- Martin, we're trying to help. - I don't want your help.
Martin,我们在试着帮你
我不用你帮
我不要别人看我.我是可怜虫!
I don't want people to look at me. I'm pathetic.
别再看我了!
Stop looking at me.
别看我了!
Stop looking at me!
给他3%的高渗溶液
Give him a three percent hypertonic solution at 500cc's per hour
接下来的4个小时需要每小时注射500 cc来稳定他
over the next four hours to stabilize him.
你以为你是个了不起的医生.
You think you're such a hotshot doctor.
你不是,你什么都不是!
You're not. You're nothing.
我要开除你
I'll fire you too.
那就开除我吧
Go ahead. Fire me.
[Inhales]
[Door closes]
我用了钥匙
I used the key.
有进步哦
That's a step.
你真的想了解我?
So you really wanna know me?
There's nothing you could reveal about yourself that I wouldn't want to know.
根本没有任何东西可以让你展示自己
这是我不想知道的
[Dog barks in distance]
这是我住的地方
This... is where I live.
我妈妈装修的
My mother decorated it.
我不洗衣服,我总是买新内裤
I don't do laundry. I buy new underwear.
看到那些桌子下面的...
And under that table?
6个月的杂志,我知道我从来不会去看
Six months of magazines I know I'll never read, but I won't throw out.
但是我不会丢掉
I don't wash dishes, vacuum, or put the toilet paper on the holder.
我不洗盘子,洗尘
或者把厕纸放到架子上
I hired a maid once. She ran away crying.
我请过一个女佣,她哭着逃跑了
我冰箱里唯一有的东西
The only things in my fridge are water, vodka, and diet soda, and I don't care.
就是水,伏特加,和无糖汽水
我不在乎.
但是你在乎
But you do.
还认为住在一起是个好主意吗?
Still think living together is a good idea?
Hey,addison让我把你们的名字放在通知书上
Hey. Addison wants me to put you guys on notice.
一旦五胞胎出生
When the quints are born we'll need everyone available.
我们需要大家都有空.
Five babies and three surgeries, we're gonna need all the hands we can get.
5个婴儿同时降生,至少有3个手术要做
我们需要所有能帮上忙的
Okay.
- OK. - Fine.
好的
那么当我们需要的时候我就呼你们?
So I'll just page you guys when we need you?
好的
- OK. - Fine.
那好吧.
- OK, then. - I was studying. What's your excuse?
我在学习,你的借口是什么?
I was staring at the ceiling in abject horror.
我在盯着那卑鄙的恐怖的天花板
我的一夜情成了个神经外科手术病例
My one-night stand is a neurosurgical case.
我听说你搞坏了他的小弟弟,牛啊
I heard you broke his penis. Nice.
我是和一些人上了床,那又怎样?
So I'm having a lot of sex. What's wrong with that?
没怎么样
Nothing at all.
那只当你开始在乎的时候才成为问题
It gets problematic when you start to care.
当你把感情放进去的时候,对吧?
When you let your emotions get in the way. You know?
对.
Yeah. Right.
[Pager beeps]
该死
Damn it.
我只要这杯茶
I'll just get the tea.
怎么了?为什么呼我?
What is it? Why'd you page me?
他开始发抖,并且说不出话来
He was acting all jittery and started slurring his words.
Martin, 能听到我吗?
Martin, can you hear me?
- [Wheezes] - [beeping]
2个单位镇静剂,应该捆起来
- He started seizing. - How much sodium did you give him?
你给他多少钠?        4个钟头给了500 cc
500cc over four hours.
事实上,医生,你下的命令是每个小时500cc,连续4个钟头
Actually, you ordered 500cc's per hour over four hours.
太快了,他的大脑涨水了
That's too fast. His brain is swelling.
我以为我说的...         为什么你不按照我说的做?
- I thought I said... - I gave you one thing to do.
我只给了你一件事做!         他会没事的,对吗?
如果他永久性虚弱
- Will he be OK? - He's currently impaired.
我无法在这种情况下做手术
I can't operate on him like this.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我并不是要让你惹麻烦
I wasn't trying to get you in trouble, but Dr. Shepherd needed to know.
但是 dr. Shepherd应该知道
这并不意味着你就不是个好医生
- It doesn't mean you're a bad doctor. - Lately, I'm crap.
是啊,最近我很糟糕
也许吧
Yeah, well, things have been kind of crappy for me too lately.
最近我的事情也变得有点糟糕
也是我的错
Also my fault.
我们都犯错
We both made mistakes.
让我问你个问题..
Let me ask you something.
当我们在一起的时候
When we were together... it was good, right?
还不错,对吗?
你是说...
You mean...
[chuckles]
是的,很好
Yeah... it was good.
很棒
It was really good.
简直...太棒了
It was pretty great.
是吧?那个有点,简单,明了
It was, wasn't it? It was like, easy, simple.
[Chuckles]
你最好戴上安全套这次.
You... better have a condom this time.
哦,在这里,s1脊椎骨上
[Derek] There it is. It's on the S1 vertebra.
移除这个瘤就会解决问题了?
[Meredith] So removing it should fix the problem?
看起来并没有什么神经损坏
[Derek] Doesn't look like there's nerve damage.
不会是任何长时期影响
There shouldn't be any long-term effect.
我已经在测试之前等了几个星期了
I'd wait a few weeks before I tested it out, though.
有意思,你是个有趣的男人
Funny. You're a funny man.
我只是不知道你们俩在约会
I just didn't know you two were dating.
你知道总有一天会发生的
You knew it would happen eventually.
最后感觉比实际感觉有些出入
"Eventually" feels a lot different than "actually."
是的,我猜是的
Yeah, I guess it does.
[Sighs]
那是令人惊讶的疼痛
Well, it's surprisingly painful.
不过好多了
It gets better.
是吗
Does it?
不知道
Well, I don't know, but I'm determined to be optimistic.
但是我下定决心要乐观面对的
你已经正式签约了? 恭喜哦
So you officially signed your contract. Congratulations.
是前进的时候了
- Time to move forward. - Yeah, it is.
是啊
我们不错,对吗?
We're OK, right?
是的,我们挺好
Yeah. We're OK.
[Pager beeps]
是dorie.
It's Dorie.
[Gasping, groaning]
怎么了?
- What's going on? - There's fetal distress.
胎儿蠕动
宫缩好疼啊!
My contractions are really hurting.
我觉得我的羊水破了!
And I think my water broke.
她的胎盘撕开了
Her placenta's tearing.
Okay,dorie,我们没办法再等了
OK, Dorie, we can't wait any longer. The babies have to come out now.
婴儿需要现在就生下来
别担心,我们会好好照顾你的
It's OK. We're gonna take really good care of you. Just keep breathing.
保持呼吸
[Rapid breathing]
uh,dorie,手术室已经做好准备了, 我们可以走了,tom在哪里?
Dorie, the OR is prepped and ready to go. Where's Tom?
他回家照看孩子去了
- He's home with the boys. - No, I called Tom. He's on his way.
不是,我给他打电话了,他正赶来
Izzie, page everyone on Dorie's team. The list is at the nurse's station.
Izzie,去把所有dorie抢救队的人都呼来
名单已经贴在护士站了
No! No!
[Shrieks]
Dorie,dorie, 你没事的
Dorie, you're fine. You're going to be fine.
你会没事的
Nothing about this is fine. It's too early. They're too hurt.
这样的情况怎么会没事!
太简单了,他们太疼了!
Dorie...
Dorie, you've carried your girls this far.
你已经带着你的女儿们这么久了
Now it's our turn. You have to trust us to bring them into the world.
现在是我们帮你的时候了
你需要相信我们,带他们来到这个世界
Tom已经在路上了吗? 是的
- Tom's on his way? - Tom's on his way.
[Groans]
Hey. Hey.
- Hey. - Hey.
我猜我要告诉你,我很高兴见到你
I'll just have to tell you I'm happy to see you.
dr. Shepherd移除了那瘤
So Dr. Shepherd removed the tumor without any complications.
没有任何并发症
So I just want to thank you. For being there for me.
我只想说,谢谢你
为我在那边
我是说,一般来说
I mean, normally, you don't expect your one-night stand
你不会想到你的一夜情会
to stick by you through a tumor.
让你发现一个瘤
- Maybe when I get out, we could... - I don't think so.
也许当我出院之后,我们可以...
我不这样认为
- Sure about that? - Yeah.
你确定吗?
You know, when I saw you at Joe's, I was just... looking for a replacement.
是的,当我在joe那里看到你的时候,我只是..
在寻找一个替代品
寻找一些东西来让我感觉好受一些.
Looking for something to make me feel better.
你应得比那更好的东西
You deserve better than that.
[Pager beeps]
[Woman on PA] Dr. Bailey, Dr. Burke to OR one. Dr. Bailey, Dr. Burke to OR one.
对不起,我要走了
Sorry. I gotta go.
- [Burke snores] - [pager beeps]
五胞胎.
Quints.
每个人都回复了,除了dr. Karev.
- Everyone answered except Dr. Karev. - Where is he?
他在哪里? 我们需要所有人!
- He was on call, he might be asleep. - Go find him.
我不知道.他昨晚值班了,也许睡着了
去把他找出来!
[Beeping]
五胞胎要出生了,我们需要你
It's time for the quints. We need you.
[Sighs]
[& James Blunt: High]
[Baby cries]
[Meredith] How do you know how much is too much?
你如何知道,多少算是多?
Too much, too soon?
太多太快
[Baby cries]
太多的信息
Too much information?
太多的娱乐
Too much fun?
Too much love?
太多的爱
太多的问题需要解答
Too much to ask?
[Baby cries]
那些太多的东西需要承受的时候
And when is it all just too much to bear?
Grey's Anatomy 210 Much Too Much  完
[Baby cries]